juniperpublishers.com 2019-04-13

# Scientific Research Journals with High Impact Articles | Juniper Publishers

### Introduction

The collection, use, storage, disclosure and correction of personal information of the Professors, Researchers etc. like Name, Email ID and University/Hospital are encrypted for maximum safety and are governed by our Juniper Staff. Here the personal information means information about an identifiable individual.

Juniper collects, stores and uses and discloses personal information about individuals in a number of circumstances set out below.

### Collection of Information

Juniper may use Google as a method of gathering required information of the individuals. It is a way for us to connect with Professors and all and is done on the basis of their Experience in the specific department and are highly secured with us.

The following information is recorded and used by the Juniper

  * Individual Name
  * Affiliation of the person
  * Country
  * Email ID

Juniper uses this information for coordinating with our Juniper publisher’s system tasks to maintain the service. 

### Confidential and personal information

We take all reasonable precautions to guard against unauthorized access to confidential and personal information including the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information held by the Juniper Publishers on its servers. When personal information is no longer required for the purposes for which it was collected it may be deleted immediately.

### Disclosure of personal information

Personal information held by Juniper will only be disclosed to only in the published articles with your consent unless the juniper is obliged to disclose information in certain circumstances.

If at any stage you provide us with your email address either as part of a message or by completing a web form, we will only use your email address for the purposes for which it was provided. We will not subscribe your email address to any external mailing list without your consent.

### Data quality/ access

Juniper will use reasonable endeavors to maintain accurate, up-to-date information regarding Editors and authors.

### Contact Us

This privacy policy is last revised on 9th May, 2016. If you want to contact us for any further information or any queries please contact us at [support@juniperpublishers.com](mailto:support@juniperpublishers.com) or even to [info@juniperpublishers.com](mailto:info@juniperpublishers.com)

### Signup Alerts

If you wish to subscribe to our Juniper Journals alerts please click here.

### Unsubscribe

If you wish not to receive emails from us please unsubscribe your email at [Unsubscribe](http://juniperpublishers.com/unsubscribe.php)
